<?xml version="1.0" ?><languages>	<language name="English" file="data_eng.xml" terms="Terms" cont="Continue" return="Return" quit="Exit"><![CDATA[Terms & ConditionsThese Terms and Conditions regulate a Customer's access to and use of the Original Technical Publications ("OTP").Acceptance of the Terms and ConditionsBy using the OTP the Customer acknowledge that he has read and agrees to be bound by these Terms and Conditions for use of the OTP DVD. The Customer further agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions of the Copyright notice or to not in any other manner use the OTP for any illegal purposes or in any manner inconsistent with these Terms and Conditions.Compliance The Customer agrees that access and use of the OTP is conditioned upon the strict compliance with these Terms and Conditions. Volvo Car Corporation reserves the right, in its sole discretion and without notice, to terminate and discontinue the Customer?s access to the OTP whenever Volvo Car Corporation is of the opinion that the Customer has committed a breach of these Terms and Conditions.Use of the OTPUnless otherwise specifically stated, all information that can be seen or read in connection with the OTP, is protected by intellectual property rights, including but not limited to copyrights, which are owned or licensed by Volvo Car Corporation. Such information may be used only in accordance with these Terms and Conditions and specifically as stated below:* Volvo Car Corporation may at any time discontinue the dissemination of the OTP and Volvo Car Corporation shall not be liable for any resulting liability, loss or damages to the Customer for discontinuing the dissemination of the OTP. * All Service Information on the OTP is directed towards trained mechanics and all use of the Service Information on the OTP, is made at the Customer?s own sole risk. * Any Service Information that is available on the OTP may be printed for the Customer's own use only. The Customer may not make copies for any other purpose. * The Customer shall use the OTP only for its individual use or in its business. The Customer agrees not to sell, transfer, assign, publish, distribute, disseminate, allow access to or convey any parts of the OTP any other information contained in the OTP, or any derivation, revision or combination thereof, to any third party. DisclaimerThe Customer uses the OTP under its own sole risk, and the Customer is solely responsible for such use. All Service Information or any other information contained in the OTP is provided "As is" and Volvo Car Corporation does not guarantee the timeliness, sequence, accuracy or completeness of the information on the OTP.The Information is produced by Volvo Car Corporation. Volvo Car Corporation shall not be held liable for the correctness of the Information or for any damage, which may ensue from incorrect contents. In particular, Volvo Car Corporation shall not be liable for any loss of profits or any other economic loss suffered by the Customer. Insofar as the liability of Volvo Car Corporation is excluded or limited, this shall apply also to the personal liability of its employees, representatives and other vicarious agents. Inasmuch as Volvo Car Corporation violates a key contractual obligation by negligence, the liability for damage to property or personal injury shall be limited to typical damages that occur.In no event will Volvo Car Corporation, its affiliates, agents and representatives be liable to you or anyone else for any decision made or action taken by you in reliance on the information on the OTP or for any consequential, special or similar damages, even if advised of the possibility of such damages.Any cause of action concerning the OTP and the information available on the OTP must be commenced within six (6) months after such cause has occurred. Nothing in these terms and conditions shall (or shall be deemed to) limit or exclude any liability that is not permitted to be limited or excluded by law. No LicenseThe Customer acquire absolutely no right or license in or to the OTP, other than the limited right to use the OTP in accordance with these Terms and Conditions.Data ProtectionThe Customer expressly consents to the collection, processing and utilization of his or her personal data by Volvo Car Corporation or its licensees for OTP. Personal data will be used in accordance with the Internet Privacy Policy of Volvo Car CorporationProvisionsIf one or several of the provisions of these Terms and Conditions should become null and void, the validity of the other provisions shall remain unaffected. In this case, the ineffective provision shall be replaced by a provision that shall correspond with the economic objective of these provisions and their associated function.Applicable Law and VenueThese Terms and Conditions and any use of the OTP be construed in accordance with and be governed by the material laws of Sweden with exclusion of the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods (CISG). The exclusive venue for all claims arising from these General Terms and Conditions shall be the district court of Gothenburg as first instance.CopyrightAll rights, including copyright and database right, in the DVD and its contents are owned by, or licensed by, Volvo Car Corporation, or otherwise used by Volvo Car Corporation as permitted by applicable law or the copyright holder.  Information on this DVD, including but not limited to text, graphics, logos, buttons, icons, images, or any underlying source code or software, may not be copied, reproduced, republished, downloaded, posted, broadcast or transmitted for any commercial or public purpose without prior written permission from Volvo Car Corporation or the copyright holder.  You may not adapt, alter or create any of the material or information in this DVD or use it for any other purpose other than for your personal non-commercial use.  You agree to use this DVD only for lawful purposes.TrademarksUnless otherwise indicated on this DVD, displayed marks, corporate logos and emblems are subject to the trademark rights of Volvo Trademark Holding AB and/or Volvo Car Corporation.]]></language>	<language name="Svenska" file="data_sve.xml" terms="Villkor" cont="Fortsätt" return="Tillbaka" quit="Avsluta"><![CDATA[Bestämmelser och villkorDe här bestämmelserna och villkoren reglerar kundens tillgång till och användning av Original Technical Publications (OTP).Godkännande av bestämmelser och villkorGenom att använda OTP bekräftar kunden att denne har läst och accepterar att styras av  de här bestämmelserna och villkoren för användning av DVD-skivan med OTP. Kunden accepterar dessutom att följa bestämmelserna och villkoren i copyright-meddelandet och att inte på något annat sätt använda OTP i olagligt syfte eller på något sätt som inte motsvarar de här bestämmelserna och villkoren.Samtycke Kunden godkänner att tillgången till och användningen av OTP är beroende av strikt efterlydnad av de här bestämmelserna och villkoren. Volvo Car Corporation förbehåller sig rätten, att helt enligt eget gottfinnande och utan meddelande, avsluta och avbryta kundens tillgång till OTP närhelst Volvo Car Corporation anser att kunden har brutit mot de här bestämmelserna och villkoren.Användning av OTPSåvida inget annat uttryckligen angetts är all information som kan ses eller läsas i anslutning till OTP skyddad av immateriella rättigheter, inklusive men inte begränsat till copyright, som ägs eller som används på licens av Volvo Car Corporation. Sådan information får bara användas i enlighet med de här bestämmelserna och villkoren och specifikt enligt vad som anges nedan:* Volvo Car Corporation kan när som helst avbryta spridningen av OTP och Volvo Car Corporation är inte ansvarigt för några resulterade förpliktelser, förluster eller skador gentemot kunden på grund av avbrytandet av spridningen av OTP. * All serviceinformation i OTP riktar sig till utbildade mekaniker och all användning av serviceinformationen i OTP görs helt på kundens egen risk. * Serviceinformationen i OTP får bara skrivas ut för kundens eget bruk. Kunden får inte i något syfte göra kopior. * Kunden ska använda OTP enbart för individuellt bruk eller i sin verksamhet. Kunden accepterar att inte sälja, överföra, tilldela, publicera, distribuera, sprida, ge tillgång till eller överlåta någon del av OTP eller annan information i OTP, eller någon härledning, omarbetning eller kombination därav, till tredje part. AnsvarsfriskrivelseKunden använder OTP helt och hållet på egen risk och kunden är ensam ansvarig för den användningen. All serviceinformation eller annan information innefattad i OTP tillhandahålls "i befintligt skick" och Volvo Car Corporation garanterar inte att informationen i OTP ges vid rätt tid, kommer i rätt ordning, är korrekt eller fullständig.Informationen framställs av Volvo Car Corporation. Volvo Car Corporation ska inte hållas ansvarigt för informationens korrekthet eller för någon skada som kan uppstå på grund av felaktig information. I synnerhet är Volvo Car Corporation inte ansvarigt för några förlorade vinster eller andra ekonomiska förluster som kunden lider. I samma grad som Volvo Car Corporations ansvar är undantaget eller begränsat gäller detta också för personligt ansvar för företagets anställda, representanter och andra ställföreträdande representanter. Såtillvida Volvo Car Corporation genom försumlighet bryter mot ett kontraktskrav ska ansvaret för skadan på egendom eller person begränsas till de direkta skador som uppstått.Inte i något fall är Volvo Car Corporation, dess dotterbolag, ombud eller representanter ansvariga gentemot dig för något av dig fattat beslut eller utförd handling som bygger på informationen i OTP eller för några därav följande, särskilda eller liknande skador, då information om risken för sådana skador tillhandahållits.Eventuella juridiska åtgärder rörande OTP och informationen i OTP måste inledas inom sex (6) månader efter att händelsen inträffat. Ingenting i de här bestämmelserna och villkoren ska (eller ska anses) begränsa eller undanta något ansvar som enligt lag inte är tillåtet att begränsa eller undanta. Ingen licensKunden erhåller inga som helst rättigheter eller någon licens till OTP, annat än den begränsade rättigheten att använda OTP i enlighet med de här bestämmelserna och villkoren.DataskyddKunden godkänner uttryckligen att Volvo Car Corporation eller dess licenstagare för OTP samlar in, bearbetar och använder dennes personuppgifter. Personuppgifterna används i enlighet med reglerna i Volvo Car Corporations sekretesspolicy för InternetKlausulerOm en eller flera klausuler i de här bestämmelserna och villkoren skulle förlora sin giltighet, ska övriga klausulers giltighet inte påverkas. I sådant fall ska den ogiltiga klausulen ersättas med en bestämmelse som motsvarar det ekonomiska syftet hos den ursprungliga klausulen och dess associerade funktion.Tillämplig lag och jurisdiktionsortDe här bestämmelserna och villkoren och all användning av OTP ska tolkas enligt och styras över av svenska egendomslagar med undantag av FN-konvention om internationella köp (CISG). Den enda jurisdiktionsorten för alla anspråk är Göteborgs tingsrätt som första instans.CopyrightAlla rättigheter, inklusive copyright- och databasrättigheter, på DVD-skivan och dess innehåll ägs av, eller som används på licens av, Volvo Car Corporation, eller används av Volvo Car Corporation på annat sätt som tillåts av tillämplig lag eller copyrightinnehavaren.  Informationen på den här DVD-skivan, inklusive men inte begränsat till text, grafik, logotyper, knappar, ikoner, bilder och all underliggande källkod eller mjukvara, får inte kopieras, reproduceras, återpubliceras, laddas ner, anslås, sändas eller överföras i något kommersiellt eller offentligt syfte utan föregående skriftligt tillstånd från Volvo Car Corporation eller copyrightinnehavaren.  Du får inte anpassa, ändra eller skapa någon del av materialet eller information på den här DVD-skivan eller använda den för något annat syfte än för din personliga, icke-kommersiella användning.  Du accepterar att använda den här DVD-skivan enbart i lagenligt syfte.VarumärkenSåvida inte annat anges på den här DVD-skivan lyder anslagna märken, företagslogotyper och symboler under varumärkesskydd som tillhör Volvo Trademark Holding AB och/eller Volvo Car Corporation.]]></language>	<language name="Deutsch" file="data_deu.xml" terms="Bedingungen" cont="Weiter" return="Zurück" quit="Ausfahrt"><![CDATA[Verkaufs- & LieferbedingungenDiese Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen regeln den Zugang eines Kunden zu Original Technical Publications ("OTP") und deren Nutzung.Annahme der Verkaufs- und LieferbedingungenDurch Nutzung von OTP bestätigt der Kunde, dass er diese Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen für die Nutzung der OTP DVD gelesen und sich verpflichtet hat, diese einzuhalten. Darüber hinaus verpflichtet sich der Kunde, die Vertragsbedingungen unter der Rubrik Copyright einzuhalten bzw. OTP keinesfalls für illegale Zwecke oder auf irgendeine Art zu verwenden, die nicht mit diesen Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen übereinstimmen.Zustimmungserklärung Der Kunde erklärt sich damit einverstanden, dass Zugang zu und Nutzung von OTP an die strenge Einhaltung dieser Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen gebunden sind. Volvo Car Corporation behält sich das Recht vor, den Zugang von Kunden zu OTP nach alleinigem Ermessen und ohne Vorankündigung zu beenden und zu unterbinden, wann immer Volvo Car Corporation zur Auffassung gelangt, dass der Kunde gegen diese Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen verstoßen hat.Nutzung von OTPWenn nicht ausdrücklich etwas anderes angegeben ist, sind sämtliche Informationen, die in Verbindung mit OTP aufgerufen oder gelesen werden können, einschließlich aber nicht beschränkt auf Copyrights, die im Eigentum von Volvo Car Corporation stehen oder von dieser lizenziert werden, urheberrechtlich geschützt. Solche Informationen dürfen nur in Verbindung mit diesen Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen verwendet werden und nur wie nachstehend ausdrücklich angegeben:?	Volvo Car Corporation kann die Verbreitung von OTP jederzeit einstellen; Volvo Car Corporation haftet dabei nicht für Verpflichtungen, Verluste oder Schäden des Kunden, die sich aus der Einstellung der Verbreitung von OTP ergeben. ?	Sämtliche Serviceinformationen von OTP richten sich an geschulte Mechaniker; jeder Gebrauch der Serviceinformationen von OTP erfolgt auf eigene Gefahr des Kunden. ?	Alle Serviceinformationen, die in OTP zur Verfügung stehen, dürfen nur für den alleinigen Gebrauch durch den Kunden ausgedruckt werden. Für andere Zwecke darf der Kunde keine Ausdrucke bzw. Kopien anfertigen. ?	Der Kunde darf OTP nur für seinen individuellen Gebrauch bzw. in seinem Betrieb verwenden. Der Kunde erklärt sich einverstanden, keinen Teil von OTP bzw. irgendeine andere in OTP enthaltene Information bzw. Herleitung, Überarbeitung oder Kombination davon an Dritte zu verkaufen, zu übertragen, abzutreten, zu veröffentlichen, zu verteilen, zu verbreiten, Zugang dazu zu erlauben oder zu übermitteln. HaftungsausschlussDer Kunde verwendet OTP ausschließlich auf eigene Gefahr und der Kunde allein ist für die Nutzung verantwortlich. Sämtliche Serviceinformationen oder sonstigen in OTP enthaltenen Informationen werden "so wie sie sind" geliefert. Volvo Car Corporation garantiert keine Rechtzeitigkeit, Abfolge, Genauigkeit oder Vollständigkeit der Informationen von OTP.Die Informationen werden von Volvo Car Corporation produziert. Volvo Car Corporation kann nicht für die Richtigkeit der Informationen oder für Schäden, die sich aus inkorrekten Inhalten ergeben könnten, zur Verantwortung gezogen werden. Insbesondere kann Volvo Car Corporation nicht für irgendwelche Gewinneinbußen oder sonstigen wirtschaftlichen Verluste des Kunden zur Verantwortung gezogen werden. Sofern die Haftung von Volvo Car Corporation ausgeschlossen oder beschränkt ist, bezieht sich dies auch auf die persönliche Haftung der eigenen Mitarbeiter, Vertreter und sonstiger stellvertretender Agenten. Sollte Volvo Car Corporation eine wichtige vertragliche Verpflichtung durch Fahrlässigkeit verletzen, beschränkt sich die Haftung für Schäden an Eigentum oder für Verletzungen auf typische auftretende Schäden.Volvo Car Corporation, ihre Tochtergesellschaften, Agenten und Repräsentanten haften Ihnen oder anderen gegenüber keinesfalls für irgendwelche Entscheidungen oder Maßnahmen Ihrerseits aufgrund von Informationen in OTP oder für Folgeschäden, spezifische oder ähnliche Schäden, auch wenn auf die Möglichkeit solcher Schäden hingewiesen wurde.Jeder Klageanspruch betreffend OTP und in OTP verfügbare Informationen muss innerhalb von sechs (6) Monaten nach Auftreten eines solchen Anspruchs eingebracht werden. Nichts in diesen Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen soll eine Haftung begrenzen oder ausschließen (oder als solches betrachtet werden), die gesetzlich nicht begrenzt oder ausgeschlossen werden darf. Keine LizenzDer Kunde hat abgesehen von seinem beschränkten Recht, OTP gemäß diesen Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen zu nutzen, keinerlei Anspruch an bzw. Lizenz für OTP.DatenschutzDer Kunde ist ausdrücklich damit einverstanden, dass seine bzw. ihre personenbezogenen Daten von Volvo Car Corporation oder deren Lizenznehmer für OTP gesammelt, verarbeitet und genutzt werden. Personenbezogene Daten werden gemäß den Internet-Datenschutzregelungen von Volvo Car Corporation verwendet.BestimmungenSollten eine oder mehrere Bestimmungen dieser Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen ungültig werden, bleibt die Gültigkeit der übrigen Bestimmungen weiter aufrecht. In diesem Fall ist die ungültige Bestimmung durch eine Bestimmung zu ersetzen, die dem wirtschaftlichen Ziel dieser Bestimmungen und den damit verbundenen Funktionen entspricht.Anwendbares Recht und GerichtsstandDiese Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen und jede Nutzung von OTP wurden unter Ausschluss des UN-Kaufrechts (CISG - United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods) in Übereinstimmung mit dem materiellen Recht Schwedens erstellt und unterliegen diesem. Ausschließlicher Gerichtsstand für alle Ansprüche aus diesen Allgemeinen Verkaufs- und Lieferbedingungen ist in erster Instanz das Bezirksgericht Göteborg.]]></language>	<language name="Francais" file="data_fra.xml" terms="Termes" cont="Continuer" return="Retour" quit="Exit"><![CDATA[Conditions généralesCes Conditions générales réglementent l'accès d'un client aux Publications techniques originales ("OTP") et leur utilisation.Acceptation des Conditions généralesEn utilisant les OTP, le Client reconnaît avoir lu et accepter d'être lié par ces Conditions générales d'utilisation du DVD OTP. En outre, le Client s'engage à être lié par les conditions générales de la Mention de réserve du droit d'auteur ou de n'utiliser d'aucune autre manière les OTP à des fins illicites ou de toute autre manière incompatibles avec ces Conditions générales.Conformité Le Client accepte que l'accès aux OTP et leur utilisation sont conditionnés par la stricte conformité à ces Conditions générales. Volvo Car Corporation se réserve le droit, à sa seule discrétion et sans préavis, de résilier et d'interrompre l'accès du Client aux OTP à chaque fois que Volvo Car Corporation considère que le client a commis une violation de ces Conditions générales.Utilisation des OTPSauf indication contraire, toutes les informations, susceptibles d'être vues ou lues en rapport avec les OTP, sont protégées par les droits de propriété intellectuelle, y compris mais non limités aux droits d'auteur, qui appartiennent à ou sont sous licence de Volvo Car Corporation. Ces informations ne peuvent être utilisées que conformément aux présentes Conditions générales et, en particulier, comme indiqué ci-dessous :?	Volvo Car Corporation peut à tout moment interrompre la diffusion des OTP et Volvo Car Corporation ne sera soumise à aucune responsabilité en résultant, ni responsable de pertes ou dommages au Client pour l'arrêt de la diffusion des OTP. ?	Toutes les Informations Service sur les OTP s'adressent à des mécaniciens formés et toute utilisation des Informations Service sur les OTP s'effectue exclusivement aux risques et périls du Client. ?	Toutes les Informations Service, disponibles sur les OTP, ne peuvent être imprimées que pour l'usage propre du Client. Le Client n'est pas autorisé à faire des copies à d'autres fins. ?	Le Client doit utiliser les OTP uniquement pour son usage individuel ou dans le cadre de son entreprise. Le Client s'engage à ne pas vendre, transférer, céder, publier, distribuer, diffuser, permettre l'accès à ou transmettre toute partie des OTP ou  toute autre information contenue dans les OTP, ou toute dérivation, révision ou combinaison des deux, à des tiers. Décharge de responsabilitéLe client utilise les OTP exclusivement à ses risques et périls, et le Client est seul responsable de cette utilisation. Toutes les Informations Service ou toute autre information contenue dans les OTP sont fournies "telles quelles" et Volvo Car Corporation ne garantit pas l'actualité, la séquence, l'exactitude ou l'exhaustivité des informations sur les OTP.Les informations sont produites par Volvo Car Corporation. Volvo Car Corporation ne pourra être tenue pour responsable de l'exactitude des informations ou ni pour tout dommage qui pourrait résulter de contenus inexacts. En particulier, Volvo Car Corporation ne sera pas tenue pour responsable de toute perte de profits ou de toute autre perte économique subie par le Client. Dans la mesure où la responsabilité de Volvo Car Corporation est exclue ou limitée, ceci s'applique aussi à la responsabilité personnelle de ses employés, représentants et autres agents d'exécution. Dans le cas où Volvo Car Corporation viole une obligation contractuelle clé par négligence, la responsabilité pour les dommages à la propriété ou des blessures sera limitée aux dommages typiques qui se produisent.En aucun cas, Volvo Car Corporation, ses filiales, agents et représentants ne pourront être tenus responsables envers vous ou envers quiconque de toute décision ou action prise par vous en se fondant sur les renseignements contenus dans les OTP ou pour des dommages consécutifs, spéciaux ou similaires, même si avisée de la possibilité de tels dommages.Toute cause d'action concernant les OTP et les informations disponibles sur les OTP doit être intentée dans les six (6) mois après qu'une telle cause a eu lieu. Rien dans ces Conditions générales ne doit (ou ne doit être réputé) limiter ou exclure la responsabilité qui n'est pas autorisée à être limitée ou exclue par la loi. Absence de licenceLe client n'acquiert absolument aucun droit et aucune licence aux OTP, autres que le droit limité d'utiliser les OTP conformément à ces Conditions générales.Protection des donnéesLe client consent expressément à la collecte, le traitement et l'utilisation de ses données personnelles par Volvo Car Corporation ou de ses titulaires de licences des OTP. Les données personnelles seront utilisées conformément à la Politique de confidentialité Internet de Volvo Car CorporationDispositionsSi une ou plusieurs des dispositions des présentes Conditions générales doivent devenir nulles et non avenues, la validité des autres dispositions restent inchangées. Dans ce cas, la disposition invalide sera remplacée par une disposition qui doit correspondre à l'objectif économique de ces dispositions et à leur fonction associée.Loi applicable et juridiction compétenteCes Conditions générales et toute utilisation des OTP seront interprétées en conformité aux et régies par les lois matérielles de la Suède à l'exclusion de la Convention des Nations Unies sur les contrats de vente internationale de marchandises (CISG). Toute réclamation relative aux présentes Conditions générales relève de la juridiction exclusive du tribunal de district de Göteborg en première instance.Droits réservésTous les droits, y compris le droit d'auteur et le droit à la base de données, sur le DVD et son contenu sont la propriété de, ou autorisés par Volvo Car Corporation, ou autrement utilisés par Volvo Car Corporation dans la mesure autorisée par la loi applicable ou le titulaire du droit d'auteur.  Les informations sur ce DVD, y compris mais non limité au texte, aux graphiques, logos, boutons, icônes, images, ou à tout autre code source sous-jacent ou de logiciels, ne peuvent pas être copiées, reproduites, republiées, téléchargées, affichées, diffusées ou transmises à des fins commerciales ou à des fins publiques sans autorisation écrite préalable de Volvo Car Corporation ou du titulaire du droit d'auteur.  Vous ne pouvez pas adapter, modifier ou créer le matériel ou les informations contenues sur ce DVD ou les utiliser à d'autres fins que pour votre utilisation personnelle non commerciale.  Vous consentez à utiliser ce DVD uniquement à des fins licites.Marques de fabriqueSauf indication contraire sur ce DVD, les marques, logos et emblèmes d'entreprises sont soumis à des droits de marque de Volvo Trademark Holding AB et/ou de Volvo Car Corporation.]]></language>	<language name="Italiano" file="data_ita.xml" terms="Termini" cont="Continua" return="Ritorno" quit="Esci"><![CDATA[Termini & CondizioniI presenti Termini e Condizioni regolano l'accesso del cliente e l'utilizzo da parte dello stesso delle Pubblicazioni Tecniche Originali ("OTP").Accettazione dei Termini e CondizioniUtilizzando le OTP il Cliente riconosce di aver letto e sottoscritto i presenti Termini e Condizioni per l'utilizzo del DVD delle OTP stesse. Il cliente inoltre sottoscrive il vincolo di conformità con i termini e condizioni della Nota sul Copyright e si impegna a non utilizzare le OTP a nessun altro scopo illegale o in qualsivoglia maniera difforme dai presenti Termini e Condizioni.Conformità Il Cliente sottoscrive che l'accesso e l'utilizzo delle OTP è condizionato all'assoluto rispetto dei presenti Termini e Condizioni. Volvo Car Corporation si riserva il diritto, a propria esclusiva discrezione e senza previa notifica, di interrompere e cessare l'accesso del Cliente alle OTP in qualsiasi momento Volvo Car Corporation stessa ritenga che il Cliente abbia commesso un'infrazione dei presenti Termini e Condizioni.Utilizzo delle OTPTranne laddove diversamente specificato, tutte le informazioni che possono essere visualizzate o lette in correlazione con le OTP sono protette da diritti di proprietà intellettuale, compresi, ma non limitatamente a, i copyright, che sono detenuti in proprietà o in licenza da Volvo Car Corporation. Tali informazioni possono essere utilizzate solo in conformità con i presenti Termini e Condizioni e specificamente come descritto qui di seguito:?	Volvo Car Corporation può in qualsiasi momento interrompere la distribuzione delle OTP senza poter essere ritenuta titolare di alcuna responsabilità relativamente a perdite o danni che il Cliente abbia a sostenere a causa della cessazione della distribuzione delle OTP. ?	Tutta la Documentazione tecnica contenuta nelle OTP è rivolta a meccanici addestrati e tutti gli utilizzi della Documentazione tecnica stessa sono posti in atto a proprio rischio e pericolo esclusivo da parte del Cliente. ?	Tutta la Documentazione Tecnica disponibile nelle OTP può essere stampata al solo scopo di utilizzo personale da parte del Cliente. Il Cliente non può realizzare copie a nessuno altro scopo. ?	Il Cliente deve utilizzare le OTP solo per il proprio utilizzo individuale nell'ambito della propria attività. Il Cliente si impegna a non vendere, trasferire, assegnare, pubblicare, distribuire, dare accesso o fornire parti delle OTP o di qualsiasi altra informazione contenuta nelle OTP, o qualsiasi derivazione, revisione o combinazione delle stesse, a nessuna terza parte. LiberatoriaIl Cliente utilizza le OTP a proprio rischio e pericolo esclusivo ed è l'unico responsabile di tale utilizzo. Tutta la Documentazione tecnica o qualsiasi altra informazione contenuta nelle OTP è fornita "Così com'è" e Volvo Car corporation non garantisce la tempestività, la sequenza, la precisione o la completezza delle informazioni in esse contenute.Le informazioni sono prodotte da Volvo Car Corporation. Volvo Car Corporation non è responsabile per la correttezza delle informazioni o per qualsivoglia danno che possa verificarsi in conseguenza di contenuti non corretti. In particolare, Volvo Car Corporation non si riterrà responsabile di alcuna perdita di profitti o perdita economica di altro genere eventualmente sofferta dal Cliente. Nella misura in cui la responsabilità di Volvo Car Corporation è esclusa o limitata, quanto sopra vale anche per la responsabilità dei suoi dipendenti, rappresentanti ed altri delegati. Nella misura in cui Volvo Car Corporation violi una clausola chiave del contratto per negligenza, la responsabilità relativa ai danni alla proprietà o alle lesioni personali sarà limitata ai danni tipici che si verificano.In nessun caso Volvo Car Corporation, i suoi affiliati, agenti e rappresentanti, potranno essere ritenuti responsabili nei confronti del Cliente o di chiunque altro per nessuna decisione presa o azione effettuata dal Cliente stesso in conseguenza delle informazioni contenute nelle OTP o per nessun danno consequenziale, speciale o simile, anche se il Cliente è stato avvertito circa la possibilità di tali danni.Qualsiasi causa di azione legale relativa alle OTP ed alle informazioni in esse contenute deve essere avviata entro sei (6) mesi dal momento in cui tale causa si è verificata. Nulla di quanto contenuto nei presenti termini e condizioni potrà (o dovrà essere ritenuto poter) limitare o escludere alcuna responsabilità che non sia possibile limitare o escludere in conformità con le leggi vigenti. Nessuna LicenzaIl Cliente non acquisisce nessun diritto o licenza relativamente alle OTP, oltre al diritto limitato di utilizzarle in conformità con i presenti Termini e Condizioni.Protezione dei datiIl Cliente acconsente espressamente alla raccolta, elaborazione ed utilizzo dei suoi dati personali da parte di Volvo Car Corporation o dei suoi titolari di licenza per le OTP. I dati personali saranno utilizzati in conformità con la Politica per la privacy in Internet di Volvo Car CorporationMisureSe una o più delle misure contenute nei presenti Termini e Condizioni dovesse diventare nulla, la validità delle altre misure non ne sarà influenzata. In questo caso, la misura inefficace sarà sostituita da una misura che corrisponderà all'obiettivo economico di queste misure e della loro funzione associata.Legge applicabile e sedeI presenti Termini e Condizioni e qualsiasi uso delle OTP sono basati su e regolati dalle leggi materiali della Svezia, ad esclusione della Convenzione delle Nazioni Unite sui Contratti per la Vendita Internazionale di Beni (CISG). La sede esclusiva per qualsiasi reclamo che origini dai presenti Termini e Condizioni Generali sarà il distretto del tribunale di Gothenburg in prima istanza.CopyrightTutti i diritti, compresi i diritti di copyright e sul database, nel DVD e sui suoi contenuti sono detenuti in proprietà o in licenza da Volvo Car Corporation, o in altro modo utilizzati da Volvo Car Corporation in conformità con la legge vigente o il detentore del copyright.  Le informazioni contenute in questo DVD, compresi, ma non limitatamente a, testi, grafica, logo, pulsanti, icone, immagini o qualsiasi software o codice sorgente di base, non possono essere copiate, riprodotte, ripubblicate, scaricate, postate, trasmesse per nessuno scopo commerciale o pubblico senza previa autorizzazione da parte di Volvo Car Corporation o del detentore del copyright.  Non è consentito adattare, alterare o creare nessuna parte del materiale e delle informazioni contenute in questo DVD o utilizzarli per scopi diversi dall'utilizzo personale e non commerciale.  Si acconsente ad utilizzare questo DVD solo a scopi legali.Marchi depositatiSalvo dove diversamente indicato su questo DVD, i marchi, i logo aziendali e gli emblemi visualizzati sono soggetti ai diritti relativi ai marchi depositati detenuti da Volvo Holding AB e/o Volvo Car Corporation.]]></language>	<language name="Español" file="data_esp.xml" terms="Términos" cont="Continuar" return="Volver" quit="Salida"><![CDATA[CondicionesLas presentes Condiciones regulan el acceso y uso por parte del Cliente de Original Technical Publications ("OTP").Aceptación de las CondicionesMediante el uso de OTP, el Cliente reconoce que ha leído y aceptado las presentes Condiciones de uso del DVD de OTP. El cliente acepta asimismo las condiciones del Aviso de derechos de autor y no utilizar en cualquier otro modo OTP para fines ilegales o no acordes en otra manera con las presentes Condiciones.Cumplimiento El Cliente acepta que el acceso y uso de OTP está condicionado por el estricto cumplimiento de las presentes Condiciones. Volvo Car Corporation se reserva el derecho, a su entera discreción y sin previo aviso, de suspender e interrumpir el acceso del Cliente a OTP si considera que éste ha vulnerado las presentes Condiciones.Uso de OTPSi no se indica específicamente lo contrario, toda la información que pueda verse o leerse en relación con OTP está protegida por derechos de propiedad intelectual, incluyendo, pero no limitado a, derechos de autor, que son propiedad o se hallan bajo licencia de Volvo Car Corporation. Dicha información deberá utilizarse únicamente de conformidad con las presentes Condiciones y específicamente como a continuación se indica:?	Volvo Car Corporation podrá en cualquier momento suspender la difusión de OTP, no pudiendo atribuírsele responsabilidad alguna por los posibles daños o perjuicios al Cliente derivados de la suspensión de la difusión de OTP. ?	Toda la información de servicio de OTP va dirigida a mecánicos cualificados, siendo el uso de la información de servicio de OTP por cuenta y riesgo del Cliente. ?	Toda la información de servicio que está disponible en OTP podrá imprimirse para uso propio del Cliente. El Cliente no podrá hacer copias para ningún otro fin. ?	El cliente deberá utilizar OTP exclusivamente para uso individual o en su negocio propio. El Cliente se compromete a no vender, transferir, ceder, publicar, distribuir, difundir, permitir el acceso o transmitir a terceros cualquier parte de OTP ni ninguna otra información contenida en éstas, así como las posibles derivaciones, revisiones o combinaciones de las mismas. Descargo de responsabilidadEl cliente utiliza OTP bajo su propia cuenta y riesgo, siendo el único responsable de tal uso. Toda la información de servicio o cualquier otra información contenida en OTP se suministra "tal cual", no garantizando Volvo Car Corporation la oportunidad, secuencia, precisión ni exhaustividad de la información de OTP.La información la produce Volvo Car Corporation. Volvo Car Corporation se exime de toda responsabilidad respecto a la exactitud de la información y sobre los posibles daños que pudieran derivarse de cualquier contenido incorrecto. Volvo Car Corporation se exime en particular de toda responsabilidad por las posibles pérdidas de ingresos o cualquier otro perjuicio económico sufrido por el Cliente. En la medida en que la responsabilidad de Volvo Car Corporation queda excluida o limitada, ello se aplicará igualmente a la responsabilidad personal de sus empleados, representantes y demás agentes indirectos. En caso de que Volvo Car Corporation vulnere una obligación contractual fundamental debido a una negligencia, la responsabilidad sobre los posibles daños materiales o personales quedará limitada a los daños típicos que se produzcan.En ningún caso, Volvo Car Corporation, sus afiliados, agentes y representantes serán responsables ante usted u otra persona por cualquier decisión o acción tomada por usted basada en la información de OTP o por cualquier daño derivado, especial o similar, incluso si se le ha advertido sobre la posibilidad de que se produzcan dichos daños.Cualquier causa de acción sobre OTP y la información disponible en éstas deberá iniciarse en el plazo de seis (6) meses después de que dicha causa se haya producido. Ningún elemento de las presentes Condiciones limitará o excluirá (ni podrá considerarse que limite o excluya) cualquier responsabilidad que legalmente no pueda limitarse ni excluirse. Inexistencia de licenciaEl Cliente no adquirirá derecho ni licencia alguna sobre OTP más allá del derecho limitado de uso de éstas conforme a las presentes Condiciones.Protección de datosEl Cliente acepta expresamente la recogida, procesamiento y utilización de sus datos personales por parte de Volvo Car Corporation o de sus licenciatarios de OTP. Los datos personales se emplearán de conformidad con la Política de privacidad para Internet de Volvo Car CorporationDisposicionesEn caso de que una o varias de las disposiciones de las presentes Condiciones fueran declaradas nulas, no se verá afectada por ello la validez del resto de disposiciones. En ese caso, la disposición no válida será sustituida por otra acorde con el objetivo económico de estas disposiciones y con su función asociada.Legislación y jurisdicción aplicablesLas presentes Condiciones y cualquier uso de OTP se interpretarán y regirán de conformidad con la legislación vigente de Suecia, excluyendo la Convención de las Naciones Unidas sobre los Contratos de Compraventa Internacional de Mercaderías (CIM). El lugar exclusivo para todas las reclamaciones derivadas de estas Condiciones Generales será la Corte de Distrito de Gotemburgo como primera instancia.Derechos de autorTodos los derechos, incluidos los derechos de autor y el derecho de bases de datos, sobre el DVD y su contenido son propiedad o se hallan bajo licencia de Volvo Car Corporation, o bien son usados por Volvo Car Corporation conforme a la legislación aplicable o con permiso del titular de los derechos de autor.  La información del presente DVD, incluyendo, pero no limitado a, texto, gráficos, logotipos, botones, iconos, imágenes, o cualquier otro software o código fuente subyacente, no podrá ser copiado, reproducido, republicado, descargado, enviado, difundido o transmitido con ningún fin comercial o de interés público sin el permiso por escrito previo de Volvo Car Corporation o del titular de los derechos de autor.  Queda prohibida la adaptación, alteración o creación de ningún material o información contenida en este DVD, así como su utilización para cualquier fin que no sea un uso personal no comercial.  Por la presente se compromete a utilizar este DVD sólo con fines legales.Marcas comercialesSi no se indica lo contrario en este DVD, las marcas, logotipos corporativos y emblemas mostrados están sujetos a los derechos de marca comercial de Volvo Trademark Holding AB y/o Volvo Car Corporation.]]></language></languages>